<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Ayush Mantra]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://ayushmantra.github.io/</link><image><url>https://ayushmantra.github.io/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Ayush Mantra</title><link>https://ayushmantra.github.io/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:20:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ayushmantra.github.io/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:20:15 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[Ajay]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>Ajay</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[About]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240914121155.png" src="https://ayushmantra.github.io/pasted-image-20240914121155.png"><br>I am Dr. Ajay Kumar, an Ayurvedic doctor from the renowned Thottakkaran Ayurveda family of Central Travancore, Kerala. My family has long been custodians of traditional Ayurvedic knowledge, and I am proud to carry forward this healing legacy. After obtaining my BAMS degree from the esteemed Vaidyaratnam Ayurveda College in Kerala, I have devoted the past 34 years to practicing and perfecting the art of Ayurveda.<br>My expertise spans the treatment of a wide range of health conditions, including cancer, kidney failure, psoriasis, paralysis, PCOD, diabetic complications, obesity, allergic problems, and respiratory issues. With profound respect for the power of food and lifestyle in healing, I believe that even chronic conditions like cancer and kidney disease can be managed effectively through Ayurvedic treatments, strict dietary discipline, and the blessings of Lord Dhanvantari, the God of Ayurveda.<br>I will be sharing my knowledge and insights on how to live an Ayurvedic life. I’ll be writing articles on natural remedies, traditional healing practices, diet, and lifestyle tips, all aimed at helping you achieve balance and wellness. Join me as I explore the ancient wisdom of Ayurveda and its application in our modern world to overcome health challenges and lead a healthier, more harmonious life.]]></description><link>https://ayushmantra.github.io/about.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">About.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 06:42:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://ayushmantra.github.io/pasted-image-20240914121155.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://ayushmantra.github.io/pasted-image-20240914121155.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ayush]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Food<br><a data-href="About" href="https://ayushmantra.github.io/about.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">About</a>]]></description><link>https://ayushmantra.github.io/ayush.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Ayush.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Ajay]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 20:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>